Order: 1 | According to the 2023 ACR guidelines for ILD, are the following recommended FOR or AGAINST as 1st li
Order: 2 | For patients receiving RTX for GPA vasculitis, what is the recommendation for PJP prophylaxis?
Order: 3 | What is the treatment for Lyme carditis?
Order: 4 | For GPA/MPA, is PLEX recommended?
Order: 5 | Describe HIDs
Order: 6 | What is the treatment of lupus DAH?
Order: 13 | What does a muscle biopsy with HCQ toxicity look like?
Order: 8 | In a patient with Behcets and hemoptysis, which imaging modality is best to assess for pulmonary art
Order: 9 | If a patient has CKD stage 3 (or 4), and needs ULT, what is the 1st line treatment?
Order: 10 | A patient taking tofacitinib is about to start ketoconazole. What to do with tofacitinib?
Order: 11 | What is the treatment for AxSpa (ankylosing spondylitis) for someone initially on TNFi, had initial 
Order: 12 | What GYN disease are SLE patients at risk of getting (females)?
Order: 7 | What is shown here? (Spine imaging)
Order: 14 | Is Tacrolimus safe in pregnancy?
Order: 15 | What type of amyloidosis can occur in patients on HD (hemodialysis)?
Order: 16 | A 28-year-old female with SLE has been stable on HCQ weight-based for many years. She has been off o
Order: 17 | A patient has newly diagnosed SLE with concomitant Class IV lupus nephritis. She was started on weig
Order: 18 | Within the 2023 ACR ILD guidelines, which is/are the recommendations classified as 'STRONGLY'?
Order: 19 | A patient on Methotrexate monotherapy for Rheumatoid arthritis is not at target and has moderate dis
Order: 20 | What is the gene involved with Haplo-insufficiency A20, which is a disease involved with dysregulati
TOTAL TRIAL: 20
