Found:  7

ID: 69a362efe212ad97bfa96a8e
Text: According to the 2023 ACR guidelines for ILD, are the following recommended FOR or AGAINST as 1st line treatment for RP-ILD (from Systemic autoimmune ...
Option 1 Expl: Methotrexate? AGAINST
Leflunomide? AGAINST
Azathioprine? AGAINST
TNFi? AGAINST
Abatacept? AGAINST
Tocilizumab? AGAINST
Nintedanib? AGAINST
Pirfenidone...

ID: 69a363a6e212ad97bfa96e9a
Text: "Triple therapy" is recommended as essentially equal to MTX + bDMARD....True of False?...
Option 1 Expl: MTX + bDMARD shows better outcomed with ACR50, with better tolerability....

ID: 69a363afe212ad97bfa96f24
Text: According to the 2023 ACR guidelines for ILD, are the following recommended FOR or AGAINST as 1st line treatment for RP-ILD (from Systemic autoimmune ...
Option 1 Expl: According to the 2023 ACR guidelines for ILD, are the following recommended FOR or AGAINST as 1st line treatment for RP-ILD (from Systemic autoimmune ...

ID: 69a363b1e212ad97bfa96f40
Text: A patient with newly diagnosed SLE has a renal biopsy which shows Class IV lupus nephritis. You decide to start triple immunosuppressive therapy inclu...
Option 1 Expl: Correct Answer....

ID: 69a363b1e212ad97bfa96f42
Text: A patient with PMH of SLE and Class IV lupus nephritis (diagnosed 1 year ago) received induction steroids followed by tapering in addition to HCQ, MMF...
Option 1 Expl: In people with ACTIVE/NEW ONSET/FLARE of Class III/IV or Class V lupus nephritis...who have achieved/sustained a complete renal response after treatme...

ID: 69a363b1e212ad97bfa96f48
Text: A patient with SLE and newly diagnosed Class IV lupus nephritis received induction steroids plus tapering, in addition to HCQ and MMF. She recently mo...
Option 1 Expl: Choice of 3rd drug (ie. belimumab or CNI) based on extra-renal symtoms (choose belimumab) vs. proteinuria (choose CNI such as voclosporin). *Could als...

ID: 69a363b2e212ad97bfa96f4a
Text: A patient with SLE and newly diagnosed Class IV lupus nephritis received induction steroids plus tapering, in addition to HCQ, MMF, and belimumab. She...
Option 1 Expl: or Add anti-CD20 agent (ie. RTX) "In people with any LN class with an inadequate renal response (i.e., have not achieved at least a partial renal resp...
