
--- Item 1 ---
ID: 69a8c6ce5dfe45eec677bfe7
Text: What do you do?
Image 1: q_non_live_vax_gc.png
Image 2: a_non_live_vax_gc.png
Summary: ACR Pregnancy Guidelines for ART in OB APS: Proceed with ART (conditional recommendation) and use prophylactic anticoagulation during procedures (strong recommendation).

--- Item 2 ---
ID: 69a733a10672ca3fa1298ed5
Text: What do you do?
Image 1: q_art_3.png
Image 2: a_art_3.png
Summary: Assisted Reproductive Technology (ART) in female RMD patients: If disease activity is low and aPL status is negative, ART can proceed as strongly recommended.

--- Item 3 ---
ID: 69a730136ee0d1f329e86192
Text: What do you do?
Image 1: q_art_2.png
Image 2: a_art_2.png
Summary: Assisted Reproductive Technology (ART) in female RMD patients with low disease activity: It is strongly recommended to continue necessary immunosuppressive treatments (except cyclophosphamide) and ensure only pregnancy-compatible medications are used during ovarian stimulation and retrieval.

--- Item 4 ---
ID: 69a72bb183c9e00ec31827e1
Text: What do you do?
Image 1: q_art_1.png
Image 2: a_art_1.png
Summary: ACR Reproductive Health Guidelines for ART: For patients with moderate to severe disease activity, ART should be deferred to optimize pregnancy outcomes and reduce risks associated with high disease activity.

--- Item 5 ---
ID: 69a71eff76003482beac663b
Text: What do you do?
Image 1: q_thrombotic_aps_1.png
Image 2: a_thrombotic_aps_1.png
Summary: ACR Reproductive Health Guidelines: Pregnancy planning for Thrombotic APS involve low dose aspirin, therapeutic heparin, and HCQ.

--- Item 6 ---
ID: 69a71b8d2a01b01eb29d29ed
Text: What do you do?
Image 1: q_ob_aps_1.png
Image 2: a_ob_aps_1.png
Summary: ACR Reproductive Health Guidelines: Pregnancy planning for OB APS involve low dose aspirin, prophylactic heparin, and HCQ, while avoiding therapeutic heparin, IVIG, or prednisone.

--- Item 7 ---
ID: 69a718d5671e7986ddd1a4ae
Text: What do you do?
Image 1: q_pos_apl_no_aps_1.png
Image 2: a_pos_apl_no_aps_1.png
Summary: ACR Reproductive Health Guidelines: Pregnancy planning for positive aPL (no APS) patients involves managing the risk with low dose aspirin while avoiding unnecessary heparin or HCQ prophylactic treatment.

--- Item 8 ---
ID: 69a715080fb35692ccca2f06
Text: What do you do?
Image 1: q_anti_ro_la_1.png
Image 2: a_anti_ro_la_1.png
Summary: ACR Reproductive Health Guidelines for Anti-Ro/La (+) patients considering pregnancy: Management includes HCQ and serial fetal echos to monitor for neonatal lupus erythematosus (NLE) and heart block.

--- Item 9 ---
ID: 69a712282e6fbd797b121cfe
Text: What do you do?
Image 1: q_preg_plan_1.png
Image 2: a_preg_plan_1.png
Summary: ACR Reproductive Health Guidelines for Pregnancy Planning: In patients with high disease activity, pregnancy should be delayed. The primary goal is to control the disease first, then reassess when disease activity is low.

--- Item 10 ---
ID: 69a711a16109ba09b02aa5f7
Text: What do you do?
Image 1: q_contraception_5.png
Image 2: a_contraception_5.png
Summary: ACR Reproductive Health Guidelines for SLE with moderate to high disease activity: Highly effective, non-estrogen options like LARCs/DMPA/progestin-only pills are strongly preferred over combined oral contraceptives. Estrogen patches are conditionally recommended against.
